Amirul Islam Al Mamun

Competitive Programmer & Student

Passionate in programming. Excellent reputation for problem solving ability, well-experienced and skilled enough in Algorithms and Data Structure. Good educational background with outstanding performance and result in each phase, improving everyday by working hard. Experienced programmer with almost 3 years of experience in programming contest and participated in almost all ICPC, NCPC, IUPC and all other programming competitions, doing great and improving. Consistently solving problems in various Online Judge.



amirulislam.bracu@gmail.com

66 Bir Uttam AK Khandakar Road, Dhaka 1212, Bangladesh

github.com/shiningflash

01521400404

in linkedin.com/in/amirulislamalmamun

shiningflash

WORK EXPERIENCE

Competitive Programmer BRAC University

02/2017 - Present

- participating in almost all ICPC, NCPC and IUPC on behalf on BRAC University
- consistently participating in Online Contests held in various Online Judges, also solving and practicing existing problems on LightOJ, Codeforces, UVa, CodeChef, Spoj etc

Contact: Moin Mostakim, Lecturer, BRAC University – 04478444060, mostakim@bracu.ac.bd

Programming MentorBRAC University ACM Chapter

05/2019 - Present

- guiding junior contestant to build up their programming skills and making them prepare for programming contest
- taking various workshops to introduce them with basic Data Structures and Algorithms
- helping them to increase their problem solving ability and providing regular guidance

Contact: Shaily Roy, Lecturer, BRAC University

Programming Contest Question Setter BRAC University

07/2019 - Present

- Intra Girls' Programming Contest Summer'19 [July 5, 2019] (platform - toph.co)
- 'Hour Of Code' Programming Contest, organized by Robotics Club [July 18, 2019] (platform - vjudge.net)

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science

Department of Computer Science and Engineering, BRAC University

12/2016 - Present

• 100% scholarship

SKILLS

Competitive Programming Problem Solving Ability

Algorithms Leadership Data Structure

Team Work Writing Skill Java

AWARDS

Champion at BUCC Intra-University Programming Contest (11/2017)

BRAC University

Contestant, bracu_silkRoad

2nd Runner Up at BUCC Intra-University Programming Contest (Senior) (02/2019)

BRAC University

Team Leader & Contestant, bucc_nahid

2nd Runner Up at BUCC Intra-University Programming Contest (Senior) (09/2018)

BRAC University

Team Leader & Contestant, SketchUP

12th at INWED Techfest Programming Contest, IUB (06/2019)

National Contest, by IEEE Bangladesh

Team Leader & Contestant, bracu_silRoad

22th in NEUB TechHunt Junior Inter University Programming Contest (11/2017)

National Contest, by Tech-Hunt

Team Leader & Contestant, bracu_kotlin

24th in AUB Inter University Programming Contest (2018)

National Contest, by Tech-Hunt

Team Leader & Contestant, bracu_silRoad

34th at DUET Inter-University Programming Contest (04/2019)

National Contest

Team Leader & Contestant, bracu_silkRoad